乔伊？
Joey?
哦 我的天啊
Oh, my God.
我答应你
Okay.
那么…
So...
我想我们应该要正式点 对吧？
...I guess we should make it official, huh?
听着 瑞秋 我
Look, Rach, I...
嘿 罗斯来了 嘿 瞧我的好朋友罗斯来了
Hey, Ross is here! Hey, look, it's my good friend Ross!
- 嘿 罗斯  - 嘿 乔伊
- Hey, Ross.  - Hey, Joey.
- 嘿 你好  - 嘿 你好
- Hey, you.  - Hey, you.
还有花耶 谢了 罗斯 我比较是那种会送糖果的人
And he brought flowers! Thanks, Ross. I'm really more of a candy kind of guy.
你今天真诡异
You're weird today.
我有事想跟你谈
Listen, I wanted to talk to you about something.
事实上 我也需要跟你谈谈
Yeah. Actually, I kind of need to talk to you too.
- 乔伊 你可以回避一下吗？- 办不到
- Joey, could you give us a minute?  - No.
- 什么？- 我很抱歉 我是说做不到
- What?  - I'm sorry. I meant, "No."
嘿 瞧瞧谁来了
Hi. Hey, look who's here.
我的孙女在哪呢？我一直在练习变魔术
Where's my granddaughter? I've been practicing my magic tricks.
他从我耳后变出一个铜板
He pulled a quarter out of my ear.
- 嘿 妈呢？- 她去接莉蒂阿姨
- Hey, where's Mom?  - She went to pick up Aunt Liddy.
莉蒂阿姨要来？那我们又可以有钱拿咯
Aunt Liddy's coming? That means we get $5 each!
我何时才可以见到艾玛 然后表演这个给她看呢？
So when do I get to meet Emma and show her this:
好耶 哇
Okay, wow.
艾玛在育婴室 如果你要 我现在就带你去
Emma's in the nursery. I'll take you now if you want.
- 但是我真的想要跟你谈谈  - 我知道 我也要跟你谈谈
- But I really want to talk to you.  - I know. I still need to talk to you.
但是在你们谈之前 我需要跟你谈谈
But before you guys do that, I need to talk to you.
还有罗斯 我需要跟你谈谈
And Ross, I need to talk to you.
- 而我需要跟你谈谈  - 谈什么？
- And I need to talk to you.  - About what?
看你知不知道他们是要谈什么
To see if you know what these guys are talking about.
--==本影片由 CMCT 团队 荣誉出品==--
更多精彩影视 请访问 http://cmct.cc
影片压制:小狮子  字幕来源:人人字幕组  调校:悠悠  招募Q号:76846146
她真是漂亮
Isn't she beautiful?
瞧瞧她 我第一个孙子
Look at her, my first grandchild.
那班算什么？
What about Ben?
哦 班 当然也是 我指的是我的第一个孙女
Well, of course, Ben. I meant my first granddaughter.
- 你有想过跟瑞秋之间的可能性吗？- 有啊…
Have you thought any more about you and Rachel?
事实上当你们进来时我本来正要问她
Yeah, actually I was gonna talk to her when you guys came in the room.
真是太好了 哇 即使我们在 你也可以开口啊
That's so exciting! Wow. You could've done that with us there.
- 是啊 没错  - 当然 是啊
- Yeah, right.  - Sure. Okay.
你能在我们面前自摸 却不能在我们面前跟瑞秋谈
You can touch yourself in front of us, but you can't talk to Rachel.
什么？我何时在你们面前摸过我自己？
What? When have I ever touched myself in front of you guys?
哦 拜托 就在不久前当你在客厅睡着时
Oh, please. Just before, when you were asleep in the lounge.
那些亚美尼亚人都不看电视反而在看你
That Armenian family was watching you instead of the TV.
这倒提醒了我 我的任天堂还在贺斯梅先生那里
That reminds me. That Mr. Hazmegian still has my Game Boy.
- 钱德 我可以跟你谈一下吗？- 当然
- Chandler, can I talk to you for a second?  - Sure.
兄弟 我刚做了一件很糟糕的事
Dude, I just did something terrible.
原来是你做的 我以为是杰克
That was you? I thought it was Jack.
不 那件事是杰克干的 瑞秋以为我跟她求婚
No, no. That was Jack. Rachel thinks I asked her to marry me.
- 什么？她为什么会那样以为呢？- 因为看起来好像是我跟她求婚了
- What? Why does she think that?  - Because it kind of looked like I did.
再说一次 什么？
Again, what?
好啦 我单膝跪在地上手中拿着戒指…
Okay, I was down on one knee with the ring in my hand...
像每个男人在一天当中的某个时候都会做的
As we all are at some point during the day.
那不是我的戒指是从罗斯的夹克掉出来的
It wasrt my ring. It fell out of Ross' jacket...
然后当我蹲下去要把它捡起来时 瑞秋以为我是在求婚
...and when I knelt down to pick it up, Rachel thought I was proposing.
罗斯准备了戒指？他要求婚？
Ross had a ring? And he was gonna propose?
- 我想是吧  - 而你抢在他之前先做了？
- I guess.  - And you did it first?
他会很不爽的 你明知道他有多爱求婚这档事
This is gonna kill him. You know how much he loves to propose.
我知道 这真是太糟糕了
I know. I know. It's awful.
那她怎么回答呢？
Well, what did she say?
她答应了
She said, "Yes."
罗斯知道吗？
Does Ross know?
哦 我的天啊 我该怎么告诉他呢？
Oh, my God. What the hell am I gonna tell him?
- 或许你根本不用告诉他  - 正合我意
- Maybe you don't have to tell him.  - I like that. Yeah.
如果你先去跟瑞秋解释清楚罗斯就永远不需要知道了
If you clear things up with Rachel, Ross never needs to find out.
但你必须在他发现而痛扁你之前赶快行动
But you have to do it before he hears about it and kicks your ass.
好吧 我们不要分心了
All right, let's not get carried away.
我想要个小孩
I want a baby.
亲爱的 我们已经讨论过了 我必须要先转过来才行
Honey, we've been over this. I need to be facing the other way.
如果我们再做爱 那我怀孕的机率就会增加一倍
If we have sex again, it'll double our chances of getting pregnant.
- 我想那问更衣室现在还是没有人  - 我好累哦
- I think that closet's still available.  - I am so tired.
- 好啦 但是说好没有前戏  - 没问题[
- Yeah, okay, but no foreplay.  - Deal!
爸 拜托
Dad, seriously!
你应该要找医生检查看看了
You know, you really should see someone about that.
知道了
Noted.
我要去找瑞秋谈谈 你自己一个人在这里没问题吧
I wanna go talk to Rachel for a minute. Are you gonna be okay alone for a bit?
你在开玩笑吗？我可以日不转睛的看着她
Are you kidding me? I could stay and look at her forever.
事实上…
Actually...
- 嘿  - 嗨
- Hey.  - Hi.
你还好吗？
Are you all right?
- 我想我刚订婚了  - 喔 天啊 他求婚了
- I think I just got engaged.  - Oh, my God! He did it?
什么？你知道他要求婚吗？
What? Did you know he was gonna ask me?
你在开玩笑吗？我就是那个怂恿他的人
Are you kidding? I'm, like, the one who talked him into it.
我喜欢当我们这群人的玩偶操纵大师
I like to think of myself as the puppet master of the group.
- 你真认为这是个好主意吗？- 我才刚怂恿了他
- And you really think this is a good idea?  - I just talked him into it.
别连你也要我怂恿才行
Don't tell me I have to do you too?
- 玩偶操纵大师也是会累的 拜托  - 好吧
- The puppet master gets tired, people.  - Okay.
我不知道 总觉得怪怪的
I don't know. It just doesn't feel right.
为什么？你们俩是注定要在一起的 大家都这么认为
Why? You two are so meant to be together. Everybody thinks so.
真的？即使罗斯也是这样想？
Really? Even Ross?
罗斯更是这样想
Especially Ross.
嘿 菲比 我等一下再回来
Hey, Pheebs. You know what? I'll come back later.
哇 这里真是拥挤
Wow. Kind of a full house here.
我想 我等一下再回来
I guess I'll just... I'll come back.
他走了 你的未婚夫
There he goes. Your fiance.
我想是啊
I guess so.
不过他会在睡着的时候自模
Although he does play with himself in his sleep.
我一点也不惊讶
I can't say I'm surprised.
- 爸 你在做什么？- 有两个人在里面做爱
- Dad, what are you doing?  - There are people in there having sex.
不可能是我 我人站在这里
It can't be me. I'm standing right here.
- 想要偷看吗？- 不要
- Wanna peek?  - No!
别这样
Come on.
你知道吗？我讨厌妈不在你身边
You know what? I don't like you without Mom.
走吧
Come on.
我们不偷看吗？
We're not peeking?
我还是要偷看
Well, I'm peeking.
哦 我的天啊
Oh, my God!
您好 您认识莫妮卡的
Hello, sir. You know Monica.
- 嘿 可以进来吗？- 当然可以
- Hey, is it okay to come in?  - Of course.
乔伊 这个戒指 我… 真是太美了 我好喜欢
Joey, this ring, I... It's beautiful. I love it.
是啊 听着 瑞秋 有件事我必须要告诉你
Yeah. Look, Rach, there's something I gotta tell you.
- 嘿  - 嗨
- Hey.  - Hi.
- 你准备好要再试喂母乳了吗？- 是啊 嗨 艾玛
- Are you ready to try nursing again?  - Yeah. Hi, Emma.
你想她为什么不吸我的奶呢？
Why do you think she won't take my breast?
没关系的 婴儿需要一点时间适应
It's all right. It takes babies a while to get it.
- 不过别担心 她会吸的  - 好吧
- But don't worry, it'll happen.  - Okay.
好的 甜心 你可以办得到的张开嘴巴 然后把它放到嘴里
Okay, sweetie, you can do it. Just open up and put it in your mouth.
救命啊 上帝
Dear Lord.
- 我很抱歉 亲爱的 你刚说什么？- 哦 对 听着 我想…
- I'm sorry, honey, what were you saying?  - Yeah, look, I think that...
因为 瞧 她又转开了
Because, look! She's pulling away again.
会不会是我的乳头对她而言太大了呢？
Do you think my nipples are too big for her mouth?
她像是被吓到了 她看起来是不是像被吓到了呢？
She looks scared. Doesrt she look scared?
你知道的 我跟她又不是很熟
You know, I don't really know her.
我们试试看按摩胸部来刺激乳汁分泌
Why don't we try massaging the breast to stimulate the flow?
- 好的  - 你在逗我吗？
- Okay.  - Are you kidding me?
真是好沮丧 她为什么不喜欢我的奶呢？
This is so frustrating. Why doesn't she want my breast?
我不知道 或许她发疯了
I don't know! Maybe she's crazy!
- 嘿 等一下  - 嗨
- Hey, wait up.  - Hi.
恭喜了
Congratulations.
我不想在乔伊面前说我不知道他是否知道
I didn't want to say anything in front of Joey. I didn't know if he knew.
什么？他不知道我们有了小孩吗？我们别太低估他了
What? That we had a baby? Now let's give him a little credit.
虽然他在稍早才吃了一个塑胶水果
Although he did eat a piece of plastic fruit earlier.
不 我是说你跟瑞秋订婚的事
No, no, that you and Rachel are engaged.
- 什么？- 哦 那是秘密吗？
- What?  - Oh, it's a secret?
太棒了 我们很久都没有玩秘密游戏了
Goody. Yes! We haven't done the secret thing in a long time.
菲比 没有什么秘密 好吗？我没有求婚
Phoebe, there is no secret, okay? I didn't propose.
你在说谎吗？
Are you lying?
是不是又跟上次一样要骗我们你是医生(博士)？
Is this like that time you tried to convince us you were a doctor?
我的确是博士
I am a doctor!
你知道吗？我要自己去跟瑞秋谈
You know what? I'm just gonna go and talk to Rachel myself.
好吧 我也是
All right. Well, me too.
- 要不要叫醒她？- 不 别这样 让她睡
- Well, should we wake her up?  - No. No. Come on, let her sleep.
- 她真的是累坏了  - 而且真的是订婚了
- She's so exhausted.  - And so engaged.
哦 我的天 她以为我们订婚了
Oh, my God. She thinks we're engaged!
为什么？她为什么认为我们订婚了呢？
Why? Why, why would she think we're engaged?
或许是因为你给了她订婚戒指吗？
Perhaps because you gave her an engagement ring?
你知道的 罗斯 博士应该要是很聪明的
You know, Ross, doctors are supposed to be smart.
- 我没有给她那个戒指  - 你没有吗？
- I didn't give her that ring.  - You didn't?
- 没有  - 那是谁的戒指呢？
- No!  - So whose ring is it?
是我的
It's mine.
- 那是订婚戒指吗？- 是啊
- Is it an engagement ring?  - Yes.
- 但是你并没有拿给她？- 没有
- But you didn't give it to her?  - No.
- 但你本来是要求婚的？- 不是
- But you were going to propose?  - No!
我可能对这件事没兴趣了
I might be losing interest in this.
听着 我妈给我那个戒指
Look. Look, my mom gave me that ring...
是因为她要我跟瑞秋求婚
...because she wanted me to propose to Rachel.
但是我只想要知道…
But all I wanted to do was see...
她是否愿意再重新开始
...if she maybe, kind of wanted to start things up again.
不冷不热的情感可真是美好啊
What beautiful lukewarm sentiment.
我不想要冲动行事 看起来她也不想要那样
I didn't want to rush into anything. It seemed like she didn't want to either.
但我不了解这是怎么发生的
But I don't understand how any of this happened.
是她在我夹克找到戒指 然后就认为我要求婚…
What, did she find the ring in my jacket, assume I was gonna propose...
便急着戴上戒指 向大家宣布吗？
...throw it on and just start telling people?
不 她说你有向她求婚
No, no. She said you actually proposed to her.
我没有 我没有求婚
Well, I didn't! I didn't propose!
除非…
Unless...
我有吗？
Did I?
我已经四十个小时没睡而…
I haven't slept in 40 hours and...
这听起来的确是我会做的事
It does sound like something I would do.
听着 我们不能永远待在这里
Look, we can't stay in here forever.
我只是不敢相信我爸看到我们在做爱
It's just, I still can't believe that my dad saw us having sex.
我的钢琴独奏会他连一次也没去 但他却看到这个
He didn't make it to one of my piano recitals, but this he sees!
没关系的 我们都是大人了 没有什么好害羞的
This is okay. We're all adults here. There's nothing to be ashamed of.
现在 我们把内裤放到口袋里 然后走出去
Now, let's put our underwear in our pockets and walk out the door.
嗨 爸
Hi, Dad.
- 我还是可以叫你爸 对吧？- 当然 我永远都是你爸
- I can still call you that, right?  - Of course. I'll always be your dad.
我只想让你知道 你在那里所看到的并非为了好玩而己
I just want you to know that what you witnessed in there, that wasrt for fun.
- 不好玩吗？- 为什么 为什么你
- It wasrt fun?  - Why, why, why would you...?
我只是不想让你认为…
Look, I just don't want you to think...
我们像动物一样 爱怎么做就怎么做
...that we're animals who do it whenever we want.
我不会那样想的
Well, I don't think that.
在今天之前 我从未想过你们会做爱
Before today, I never thought of you two having sex at all.
还是以前较简单
It was a simpler time.
事实上是 爸 我们正在努力
The truth is, Dad, we're trying.
- 什么？- 是啊 我们正在努力要怀孕
- What?  - Yeah, we're trying to get pregnant.
哦 我的天啊 这真是太好了
Oh, my God, this is so exciting.
那再进去里面 我来看门
Well, get back in there! I'll guard the door!
没关系 爸 我们可以等
That's okay, Dad, we can wait until later.
哇 我可不这么认为 你不是正在排卵吗？
Whoa! I don't think so. Arert you ovulating?
爸
Daddy!
你要把握时机 小公主
You gotta get at it, princess.
当你妈跟我试着要怀你的时候…
When your mother and I were trying to conceive you...
只要她在排卵 我们就做
...whenever she was ovulating, bam, we did it!
这就是为什么我的臀部会不好
That's how I got my bad hip.
真好笑 这个对话就是关于我的头怎样被一颗子弹穿过
That's funny. This conversation's how I got the bullet hole in my head.
有一次我把膝盖放到洗手台上 而你妈…
This one time I had my knee up on the sink, and your mother was...
我想我们不需要知道你跟妈的特殊姿势
I don't think we need to hear the specific positions you and Mom had sex.
没错 应该要讨论你们的姿势才对
You're right. This is about your positions.
我刚在更衣室里面看到的 并非
Now, what I saw in the closet is not the optimum position...
最佳受孕姿势
...for conceiving a child.
- 虽然那感觉可能会很棒  - 我现在一点也感觉不出来
- Although it might feel good.  - I don't feel good right now.
但是快感是很重要的 而且如果女人有高潮是会有帮助的
But pleasure is important, and it helps if the woman has an orgasm.
你要接受任务了吗？小子
You up to the task, sailor?
- 嘿  - 嘿 哦 我需要告诉你一件事
- Hey.  - Hey. Oh, I need to tell you something.
现在就正是时候我正要去把我的耳朵切掉
Well, now's a good time. I'm on my way to have my ears cut off.
乔伊要我嫁给他
Joey asked me to marry him.
- 什么？- 乔伊向我求婚
- What?  - Joey proposed to me.
- 他疯了吗？你才刚生下罗斯的孩子  - 我答应了
- Is he crazy? You just had Ross' baby!  - Well, I said yes.
什么？你疯了吗？你才刚生下罗斯的孩子
What, are you crazy? You just had Ross' baby!
这真是太不配了 不 这更糟 这是不对的
It's so inappropriate. No, it is worse than that. It is wrong.
而且比我的还大
It is bigger than mine!
我知道 《我们的日子》真是太感谢电视了
I know. Days of our Lives, thank you very much.
- 你不能嫁给他  - 为什么不能？
- You can't marry him.  - Why not?
我不想要一个人苦撑 而且他是个好人
Come on, I don't want to do this alone, and he's such a sweet guy.
而且他很爱我
And he loves me so much.
那你爱他吗？
Well, do you love him?
当然
Sure.
- 当然？- 是啊 我是说 随便啦
- Sure?  - Yeah, I mean, whatever.
亲爱的 问题是
Honey, the question is...
你是真的想嫁给乔伊吗？
...do you really want to marry Joey?
不是
No.
不 我不想
No, I don't.
你可以好心一点帮我去告诉他吗？
Could you be a dear and go tell him?
你还没有告诉瑞秋你不是在求婚？
You still haven't told Rachel you werert proposing?
还没有 她戴上了戒指
No. She had the ring on...
她看起来很兴奋 然后她露出胸部
...she seemed so excited, and then she took her breast out.
乔伊 你得要告诉她事实真相 胸部看起来怎样？
Joey, you have to tell her what's going on. And what did it look like?
我没有看到
I didn't look at it.
被那笨小孩的头挡住了
The stupid baby's head was blocking most of it.
在罗斯发现之前 马上去跟瑞秋说
Go and tell Rachel right now, before Ross finds out.
听着 事情没那么简单 她说她想要嫁给我
Look, it's not that easy. She said she wanted to marry me.
我不想要伤害她
I don't want to hurt her.
好啦 听着 反正就是温和地告诉她
Okay, look, just do it gently.
你说的没错
You're right.
没错 我得在罗斯知道之前赶快告诉她 我会温和地告诉她
You're right. I'll go tell her now before Ross finds out, and I'll be gentle.
我办得到的 我是个温和的人
I can do that. I am a gentle person.
对了 有两个人在那里面胡搞 你可以瞧瞧
By the way, two people screwing in there if you want to check that out.
嘿
Hey.
我听说订婚的事了
Listen, I heard about the engagement.
惊讶吧？
Surprised?
而且很困惑
And confused.
瑞秋 甜心
Rach, sweetie...
我没有向你求婚
...I didn't propose to you.
我知道
I know.
我想你不知道
I don't think you do.
你没有向我求婚
You didn't propose to me.
是乔伊向我求婚
Joey did.
可怜的宝贝 你累坏了
Poor baby, you're so tired.
瑞秋 我没有向你求婚
Rach, I didn't propose to you.
乔伊没有向你求婚
Joey didn't propose to you.
钱德也没有向你求婚
And Chandler didn't propose to you.
你没有向我求婚
You didn't propose to me.
钱德没有向我求婚
Chandler didn't propose to me.
但是乔伊有
But Joey did.
乔伊跟你求婚？
Joey proposed to you?
- 我可以等一下再回来  - 等一下 等一下
- I can come back.  - Wait. Wait. Wait.
- 乔伊 你有跟她求婚吗？- 没有
- Joey, did you propose to her?  - No.
- 你有  - 事实上 技术上而言 我没有
- Yes, you did.  - Actually, technically, I didn't.
- 那你为什么给我戒指呢？- 等一下
- Well, then, why did you give me a ring?  - Wait.
- 你给她戒指？- 木有 而且我也没向她求婚
- You gave her the ring?  - No, and I did not ask her to marry me.
- 有 你有  - 不 我没有
- Yes, you did.  - No, I didn't.
- 你有  - 我没有
你有 别再说你没有了
Yes, you did, and don't you say you didn't!
他就在这里 单膝跪下来 然后跟我求婚
He was right there. He got down on one knee and he proposed.
- 你跪了下去？- 是啊 逊毙了
- You were down on one knee?  - Yeah, that looks bad.
但是我并没有求婚
But I didn't propose.
- 那到底是怎么回事？- 是啊 到底是怎么回事？
- Then what did happen?  - Yeah, what did happen?
是这样的 戒指掉到了地上 然后我蹲下去捡…
Okay, the ring fell on the floor, and I went down to pick it up...
然后你就以为我是在求婚
...and you thought I was proposing.
但是你有说"嫁给我好吗？"
Yeah, but you said, "Will you marry me? "
- 不 我没说  - 有 你有
- No, I didn't.  - Yes, you did.
- 不 我没有  - 有 你有 哦 天啊 你并没有
- No, I didn't.  - Yes, you did. Oh, my God, you didn't.
- 你为什么不早点说呢？- 我有试着…
- Why didn't you tell me that before?  - Well, I tried...
但是一直有人打断 然后你又露出胸部
...but people kept coming in, and then you took your breast out.
你看到她的胸部了？
You saw her breast?
我待会再告诉你 冷静点
I'll tell you about it later. Be cool.
那你拿个戒指干什么呢？
Then what the hell were you doing with an engagement ring?
那不是我的戒指 是罗斯的
It wasrt my ring! It's Ross' ring.
这就是为什么我好难过 瑞秋因为本来是他要求婚的
That's why I felt so bad, Rach, because he was gonna propose.
什么？
What? !
你本来要跟我求婚？
You were gonna propose to me?
没有
No.
哦 这真是尴尬
Well, this is awkward.
但是我本来是要问你是否愿意再重新开始
But I was going to see if, you know, maybe you wanted to start dating again.
- 但是 只不过是这样 瑞秋  - 老兄 加点油吧 我都求婚了
- But that, I mean, that was all, Rach.  - Dude, step up. I proposed.
不 你没有
No, you didn't.
没错 发生太多事了 我想我一定是吃了什么坏掉的水果
That's right. There's a lot going on here, and I think I ate some bad fruit earlier.
嘿 她刚醒来 而且饿了 我们再来试试看吧
Hey, she just woke up. She's hungry. Why don't we give this another try?
我不敢相信你竟然告诉她我要求婚
I can't believe you told her I was gonna propose.
- 我不敢相信你并没有要求婚  - 嘿 我不想要急着做什么
- I can't believe you're not gonna.  - Hey, I am not gonna rush into anything.
是啊 老兄 我完全可以理解
Yeah, dude, I totally understand.
通常在我跟一个女人生了小孩之后 我也会想要放慢脚步的
Usually after I have a baby with a woman, I like to slow things down!
- 哦 天啊  - 怎样？
- Oh, my God!  - What?
她在吸了 她在吸奶了
She's doing it! She's breast-feeding!
真是太美妙了
It's beautiful.
- 我等一下再回来  - 谢谢
- I'll come back for her later.  - Thank you.
- 哇 感觉真奇怪  - 怎样 是好的奇怪吗？
- Wow, this feels weird.  - What, good weird?
棒透了的奇怪
Wonderful weird.
你们知道吗？我也要走了
You know what, you guys? I'm gonna go too.
我很抱歉
And I'm sorry about everything.
- 亲爱的 别担心 是我的错  - 不 瑞秋 我应该早点告诉你的
- Honey, don't worry, it was my mistake.  - No, Rach, I should've told you sooner.
只不过…
It's just that...
天啊 这熊孩子真是厉害啊i
Man, that kid is going to town!
她真是完美
She's perfect.
我们真幸运
We're so lucky.
我们真的很幸运
We really are.
听着 我知道这不是求婚 而且我也不知道你的意思如何
Look, I know it's not a proposal, and I don't know where you are...
但是有了艾玛之后一切的事 我…
...but with everything that's been going on and with Emma, I'm...
- 我一直感到… 是的 我知道
- I've been feeling...  - Yeah, I know.
我一直感到…
I've been feeling...
- 是吗？- 是啊
- Yeah?  - Yeah.
好的 那么 那… 哇 好的 那么
Okay, well, that... Wow, okay, well...
那么或许我们可以再考虑在一起？
Then maybe at least we can talk about us again?
是啊 或许
Yeah. Maybe.
那 很好 好的
Well, good. Okay.
我有点想 你知道的 如果我们 如果…
I kind of think, you know, if we, if...
你手上戴着戒指
You're wearing the ring.
你说什么？
What's that?
你告诉菲比你订婚了
And you told Phoebe you were engaged.
很抱歉 你说什么？
I'm sorry, what?
当你以为乔伊是在求婚…
When you thought Joey proposed...
你有答应吗？
...did you say yes?
孩子们 我跟医生谈过 拿了这些怀孕须知的传单给你们
Kids, I spoke to a doctor and picked up these pamphlets on how to get pregnant.
- 嗨 爸  - 嗨
- Hey, Dad.  - Hi.
很抱歉再打扰你们 但是可不可以把我的传单递出来呢？
Sorry to bother you again, but could you pass my pamphlets back?
谢谢
Thank you.